No offense, but I've known
the guy a really long time.
(Amy:)Well, I've, you know,
(Amy:)seen him without pants on.
Again, no offense,
but so have I.
(Amy:)Well, he's seen me
without pants on.
(Leonard:)Again, no...
(Penny:)Okay, this is ridiculous.
(Penny:)(knocking)
(Amy:)Sheldon?
(Penny:)Can I come in?
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)How do you know I'm not using
the facilities?
(Penny:)Because you e-mail me your
bathroom schedule once a week,
(Penny:)even though
I've clicked unsubscribe,
(Penny:)like, a thousand times.
(Amy:)So...
(Penny:)what's going on?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
I-I looked around the room,
(Sheldon:)and I saw all the faces
and the presents,
(Sheldon:)and it... it was just too much.
(Penny:)I get that.
(Penny:)Hey, you want to just bring
a few people in here?
(Sheldon:)You know,
Wil Wheaton in the bathtub,
(Penny:)Batman on the toilet.